Look at the generations, today we are seeing a rise of about three percent.
A
report has also come on the company. A report has come from the researcher of Goldman Sachs
report, Credit Suisse
and here they say that there is
talk of getting a lot of benefit from the product launches and we are watching it morning and evening
and on this report the
stock is also positively rejecting and
now gradually it has come up by three percent.
This city Suchita is trading around 1257.
What is also increasing to you? There
is Jyoti on ICICI Lombard. Are you looking for any train?
You should remain in the stock at this time.
Hello friends, not now. This is a
very
amazing position for the short term.
In the last few days, it has been from 1360 to
1240. Audit waste collection came and there was
a strong support back around 1240. This and
placement around 120
is a very important support around 1220. So exit poll wave
race kidnapping, they will not add that in the near
term you will get a very big deal in which but will
convert these into roadies.
In this, a good support will remain around 1220 for 14 years. So, if there is an
acting portion by keeping a stop loss below 1210, then I would
advise to hold them. Okay,
keeping contact with 1000, the
stop loss is visible here. The truth is also being
formed for you and you Chiku Singh, how to
see the nipple, what is the ice?
Last week on Tuesday, we had a
big issue in the market when the spy
spy expressed anger on tomatoes with a rise of 10 points,
but that was from last Tuesday,
but so far today this week has been a gathering, but till now the
market is
reading within the same range which was formed in a big range last Tuesday, in this respect, there is a
correction in the global market, so we are
not getting network here, but
this time we are going to Twitter again, so
here this is a clear indication, our market
knows this correction at one time, now the
next point is not rising here
because the data is
not supporting the market for a big rise.
So for example, if you take a position in a file,
backward index futures have
most of the positions created on the short site, all this
in the temple series. Now if we look at yesterday's data, then
almost 98% of the positions
are on its right side and 80 percent of the population is on
their short site. Technique of making a tweet on the dollar
index. In this, we are watching good TV. So,
when the big teams in the dollar index have a connection
related to our market, it gives a
connection because if we
delete the university from it, then the doctor has given
this bullishness to our market. Another
fact is that the Indians were not allowing it to go up,
but if you look at the market friend, then the
market is positive in the entire size and control subject. So, this is a clear
indication that
after 18,000,
like the correction that is happening this time and the
reaction of the time buyers, the prices will
not correct, which we feel will remain
in the range
17517 40 Limited Character Support Range
Market People. Until this support range is not there, then there will be a
big price  There will be no rate correction
and from above or cold here the call
reference etc. is collective and it will remain graduation
so if you want to trend in the index then it is
better this will be the market of options jewelers
because when the big mood does not
come then you can enter both the add 1760 and Mani
Kaul point both the options can work for the country,
they can also avoid the call on seven training
because when the market is
in the range and the previous current will go to the body in future, the
commander-in-chief of both
is around 170, start both of these, earning 250 has been done, it
remains in the range here, so collect first so that
you can save this cream Singh till morning,
targets can now be activated
on the index, so you have understood your marriage based
decision completely till the last moment, you can say that to a large
extent you have told the shop view.